<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hair on Brisuthi</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/categories/hair/</link><description>Recent content in Hair on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:13:38 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/categories/hair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intensive Hair Mask</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/intensive-hair-mask/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 14:00:37 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/intensive-hair-mask/</guid><description>Enrich is an intensive anti-hairloss hair mask blending the most exotic, beneficial oils proven for hair revitalization. Enrich works to significantly improve dry/damaged and brittle hair. Precise amounts of fatty acid-rich plant oils from Japanese Tsubaki oil and organically-wildcrafted Pacaxi oil and potent active herbal infusions, including Waratah extract and sandalwood extract create a powerful synergy to build keratin and dramatically soften, restore shine, elasticity, and manageability.</description></item><item><title>L&#39;Huile De Ungurahua Hair Treatment Oil</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/l-huile-de-ungurahua-hair-treatment-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:58:37 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/l-huile-de-ungurahua-hair-treatment-oil/</guid><description>Organically-wildcrafted Ungurahua oil is an exceptional hair treatment which can addresses scalp problems, especially itchy dandruff and hair loss. It stimulates and regenerates follicle cells, thus controlling scalp disorders caused by bacterial infections and increasing circulation and capillary strength. Infused with Organically-wildcrafted Pequi Oil which has amazing capacity to restore the hair&amp;rsquo;s fiber after chemical and heat damage. It brings back silkiness, malleability, and shine to the hair while an exclusive blended essential oil helps stimulate hair growth and keeps scalp healthy.</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Argan Oil Treatment Shampoo</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/moroccan-argan-oil-treatment-shampoo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:57:01 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/moroccan-argan-oil-treatment-shampoo/</guid><description>Indulge with our cult product Moroccan Argan Oil Treatment shampoo, the exceptional hair treatment. Harnessed with Organic Moroccan Argan oil, this high performing shampoo gently cleanses your hair and leaves your hair soft, silky and light-reflecting. The Lioleic acid content balances your scalp, promotes hair growth and prevents hair loss. Blended with therapeutic grade essential oils, including Rosemary, Cedarwood, Lavender, Tea tree oil, This combination helps enhance hair growth, stimulate the hair follicles by increasing circulation to the scalp and slow hair loss.</description></item><item><title>Persian Habbatus Oil Treatment Shampoo</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/persian-habbatus-oil-treatment-shampoo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:55:57 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/persian-habbatus-oil-treatment-shampoo/</guid><description>The Habbatus Sauda is an amazing wonder plant that continues to cause ripples around the world. The oil contains Thymoquinone and Alpha-hederin and various Amino acids that help strengthen hair by consolidating the roots. Its antidandruff and antimicrobial properties promote healthy scalp and reduce scalp itchiness. This oil shampoo cleanses your hair without drying, leaving hair silky-touch, healthy and shining.</description></item></channel></rss>