<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Brisuthi</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 18:09:59 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brisuthi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>African Baobab Oil Treatment Cleanser</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/african-baobab-oil-treatment-cleanser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 19:43:12 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/african-baobab-oil-treatment-cleanser/</guid><description>Our cult product African Baobab Oil Cleanser gently dissolves all makeup, helps unclog pore and leaves skin remarkably clean, refreshed and balanced without a trace of makeup. Infused with “Tree of life “Organic Baobab oil which is very rich in nutrients – contains all three omega fatty acids: omega 3, 6 and 9, as well as containing some rare fatty acids and a host of vitamin A, C, D, E and combined with organic Hempseed oil and organic Sacha Inchi oil which has the highest amount of Liolenic acid in the world.</description></item><item><title>French Geranium Foaming Cleanser</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/french-geranium-foaming-cleanser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 19:41:31 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/french-geranium-foaming-cleanser/</guid><description>This Sulfate-free foaming cleanser gently dissolves impurities without striping moisture. Its pH equals to pure water (pH7) and provides you delicate lather. Formulated with soothing agent and natural extracts, along with Geranium essential oil, Rose damascus, Roman Chamomile, Cactus and Royal lotus pollen extract. This cleanser is suitable for all skin types, even acne-prone skin.</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Saffron Water</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-saffron-water/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:40:51 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-saffron-water/</guid><description>Organic Moroccan Saffron is a well-known for the most expensive spice and has a lot of health benefits and therapeutic values. The subtly aromatic spice is one of the most prominent ingredients used in skin lightening agent due to copper, magnesium, potassium, magnese, iron, selenium, zinc as well as vitamin C, riboflavin,niacin (vitamin B), folic acid and vitamin A contents. Formulated with organic Aloe vera Barbadensis Miller which contains both Aloin A and B, This Essence water can help skin reach its youthfully radiant.</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Rose Damascus Water</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-rose-damascus-water/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 19:43:32 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-rose-damascus-water/</guid><description>Made by hand in Morocco by one of the oldest women’s co-operatives, using only the finest roses which have been grown organically in a pesticide free zone. The water is triple distilled, filtered and infused with rose petals. This is a 100% natural and organic product. Free from parabens, preservatives, fragrances, binders, additives, colorants and any other nasties. Our 100% pure and Certified Organic by Ecocert Moroccan Rose Damascus water contains natural anti-inflammatory properties to reduce redness and skin irritation, soften, balance and regenerate your face, as well as tighten and minimize pores.</description></item><item><title>Sandalwood Exfoliating Mask</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/sandalwood-exfoliating-mask/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:15:52 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/sandalwood-exfoliating-mask/</guid><description>A super fine sandalwood exfoliating mask loaded with organic extracts gently polishes, refines, and improves the appearance of skin’s texture while Pink Brazilian clay helps unclog pores and remove all impurities and toxins to reveal a brighter and younger looking complexion.</description></item><item><title>Le Mask Noir</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-mask-noir/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:14:33 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-mask-noir/</guid><description>The Rinse-off mask is formulated with Ghassoul clay which forms naturally in the Atlas regions of Morocco. This clay has been used for centuries as a tradition to gently cleanse impurities from the skin and hair. Rich in vitamins, minerals and trace elements such as iron, zinc, magnesium, phosphorous. Ghassoul has cleansing, soothing, absorbing and regenerative properties. Infused with Cactus extract, Glabridin derived naturally from Licorice root and various organic and natural extracts, This intensive clay mask contains high levels of antioxidants that calm inflammation and promotes skin radiance.</description></item><item><title>Aboriginal Citrus Concentrate</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/aboriginal-citrus-concentrate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:03:45 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/aboriginal-citrus-concentrate/</guid><description>Superior potency with highest concentrations of natural Phyto-actives derived from organic plants with innovative cellular extraction. This concentrate serum contains Murunga extract (a native tree from Australia) which is the richest source of natural Vitamin C found in nature and provide Phyto-active compounds, including Gallic acid and Flavone Glycoside which helps stabilize Vitamin C. Combined with Finger lime caviar extract which boasts the great amount of Ferulic acid, Coumarin and Tryptophan, This powerful global anti-aging concentrate helps rejuvenate skin.</description></item><item><title>White Cypress Intensive Radiance Treatment Serum</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/white-cypress-intensive-radiance-treatment-serum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:01:20 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/white-cypress-intensive-radiance-treatment-serum/</guid><description>An fast-correcting serum clinically proven to combat hyper-pigmentation, fade dark spots and repair sun damage, formulated with a powerful blend of organic actives &amp;amp; nutrients, including White Cypress, Snowflower, Desert lime and Davidson plum, which provide full profile of Phyto actives; Procyanidin, Epicatechin, Kaempferol. To ensure the fast acting, this serum is fomulated with a traditional Chinese herb Rheum rhaponticum root extract which tightly controls melanin synthesis. Within 2 weeks of consistent use, skin looks visibly brighter, more luminous and toned.</description></item><item><title>Kalahari Global Anti-Aging Treatment Oil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/kalahari-global-anti-aging-treatment-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:55:13 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/kalahari-global-anti-aging-treatment-oil/</guid><description>The global anti-aging treatment, infused with organic Melon, Watermelon and Guava seed oil from Kalahari Desert of Namibia is a rich natural source of broad-spectrum antioxidants (A, B, C, D, E, F) amino Acids glutamate and tryptophan acid and vital minerals. It can visibly lift, tone and tighten skin with natural Arginine and Lysine. These peptides relax facial muscles just like having a Botox. Thanks to its rich Omega 6 fatty acids, the oil penetrates deeply to help rejuvenate and create healthy glowing skin by stimulating skin cell growth and restructuring skin cells to keep skin supple, firm, and youthfully radiant.</description></item><item><title>Huile De Nuit</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/huile-de-nuit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:53:30 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/huile-de-nuit/</guid><description>Huile de nuit is an exceptional global anti-aging treatment with organically wild-crafted Buriti oil (the richest natural source of pro-vitamin A), super-antioxidant Açaí fruit oil and exceptional antiaging cacay oil. Thanks to its vitamins and minerals concentrate, This Oil fight all signs of aging and helps visibly promote luminosity, replenish moisture, restore elasticity, and remarkably repair lines and wrinkles. After few nights of use, skin is gently retexturized and rejuvenated, leaving a brighter, luminous, healthy-looking complexion in the morning</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Prickly Pear Oil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-prickly-pear-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:44:51 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-prickly-pear-oil/</guid><description>The heritage of Morocco Prickly pear seed oil, one of the most expensive oils in the world contains almost 150% more vitamin E than Argan oil. This naturally occurring antioxidant acts as a free radical scavenger, preventing them from causing damage that leads to signs of aging. It benefits the skin with it’s exceptional hydrating, brightening and global anti-aging properties. The production of premium Prickly Pear Seed Oil is incredibly labour intensive and time consuming — it takes nearly 30 kilograms of seed, or 8 tons of the fruit, to produce just one litre of oil.</description></item><item><title>La Creme Intensive Global Anti Aging Treatment</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-creme-intensive-global-anti-aging-treatment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:12:12 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-creme-intensive-global-anti-aging-treatment/</guid><description>The exquisite modern gel-cream is designed to combat all signs of aging. An intelligent formula is infused with innovative NoHyal, a new generation of Hyaluronic acid which is more efficient than Retinol. Combined with organic Ximenynic acid-rich Sandalwood seed oil, this cream can reduce fine lines, improve skin tone, provide long-lasting hydration and increase dermal strength. While other organic extracts help retexturize and reveal more youthful and brighter skin. Moreover, French Melon extract provides the exceptional protection from aggressive environment with SOD, one of the most powerful antioxidants.</description></item><item><title>Balloon Vine Intensive Repair Treatment</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/brazillian-balloon-vine-intensive-repair-treatment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:08:25 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/brazillian-balloon-vine-intensive-repair-treatment/</guid><description>Harness the power of the nature with organic Balloon vine extract and 12 powerful plant extracts, This intensive repair treatment create a complex that reduces inflammation and Irritation, protects and stabilizes the aggrieved skin-barrier with natural Phytosterols which can effectively reduce inflammation, almost equal to 0.1% hydrocortisone while antioxidants soothe and effectively addresse skin problems, including redness, itchiness or chronic breakouts. It works strategically to strengthen the skin in order to achieve a healthy and flawless skin.</description></item><item><title>La Creme Yeux Concentrate Eye Contour Treatment</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-creme-yeux-concentrate-eye-contour-treatment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:58:35 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-creme-yeux-concentrate-eye-contour-treatment/</guid><description>An exceptional nourishing eye cream rich in advanced natural extracts, including Super green Broccoli extract and Mountain Pepper berry,that work to instantly make skin around the eyes look smoother and firmer. Infused with Hyalusphere® encapsulated in a patented Spherulite and Arabica green coffee bean extract which has an incredible high level of chlorogenic acid, a powerful antioxidant. This eye treatment can obviously help reduce the look of fine lines, dark circles, and puffiness.</description></item><item><title>Le Soleil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-soleil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:13:39 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-soleil/</guid><description>The revolutioary Le Soleil The ultimate protection uses a specially developed proprietary enwrapping technique to stabilize the organic sunscreens and to ensure high performance with prolonged and consistent SPF values. The aqueous encapsulated Sunscreen is non-irritant and not absorbed into the skin, and can also provide a longer skin surface residence time as well as reproducible SPF values with broad spectrum protection (PA++++). Formulated with one of the most Super antioxidants, Hydroxytyrosol and Oleuropein naturally derived from olive fruit and leaf, the sunscreen helps preserve the skin’s ability to protect against the sun and photo-aging due to a combination of cutting-edge protective super antioxidant ingredients and natural Ectoin and SOD, one of the most powerful antipollution agent.</description></item><item><title>Reward</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/liff/reward/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2019 09:06:49 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/liff/reward/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Intensive Hair Mask</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/intensive-hair-mask/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 14:00:37 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/intensive-hair-mask/</guid><description>Enrich is an intensive anti-hairloss hair mask blending the most exotic, beneficial oils proven for hair revitalization. Enrich works to significantly improve dry/damaged and brittle hair. Precise amounts of fatty acid-rich plant oils from Japanese Tsubaki oil and organically-wildcrafted Pacaxi oil and potent active herbal infusions, including Waratah extract and sandalwood extract create a powerful synergy to build keratin and dramatically soften, restore shine, elasticity, and manageability.</description></item><item><title>L&#39;Huile De Ungurahua Hair Treatment Oil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/l-huile-de-ungurahua-hair-treatment-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:58:37 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/l-huile-de-ungurahua-hair-treatment-oil/</guid><description>Organically-wildcrafted Ungurahua oil is an exceptional hair treatment which can addresses scalp problems, especially itchy dandruff and hair loss. It stimulates and regenerates follicle cells, thus controlling scalp disorders caused by bacterial infections and increasing circulation and capillary strength. Infused with Organically-wildcrafted Pequi Oil which has amazing capacity to restore the hair&amp;rsquo;s fiber after chemical and heat damage. It brings back silkiness, malleability, and shine to the hair while an exclusive blended essential oil helps stimulate hair growth and keeps scalp healthy.</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Argan Oil Treatment Shampoo</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-argan-oil-treatment-shampoo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:57:01 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-argan-oil-treatment-shampoo/</guid><description>Indulge with our cult product Moroccan Argan Oil Treatment shampoo, the exceptional hair treatment. Harnessed with Organic Moroccan Argan oil, this high performing shampoo gently cleanses your hair and leaves your hair soft, silky and light-reflecting. The Lioleic acid content balances your scalp, promotes hair growth and prevents hair loss. Blended with therapeutic grade essential oils, including Rosemary, Cedarwood, Lavender, Tea tree oil, This combination helps enhance hair growth, stimulate the hair follicles by increasing circulation to the scalp and slow hair loss.</description></item><item><title>Persian Habbatus Oil Treatment Shampoo</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/persian-habbatus-oil-treatment-shampoo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:55:57 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/persian-habbatus-oil-treatment-shampoo/</guid><description>The Habbatus Sauda is an amazing wonder plant that continues to cause ripples around the world. The oil contains Thymoquinone and Alpha-hederin and various Amino acids that help strengthen hair by consolidating the roots. Its antidandruff and antimicrobial properties promote healthy scalp and reduce scalp itchiness. This oil shampoo cleanses your hair without drying, leaving hair silky-touch, healthy and shining.</description></item><item><title>Egyptian Myrrh Bath Oil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/egyptian-myrrh-bath-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:53:56 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/egyptian-myrrh-bath-oil/</guid><description>Indulge yourself with a luxurious bathe exprerience to pamper, and moisturize the skin. Treat your body to a relaxing bath in our unique scent blended with Egyptian myrrh oil and uplifting Rosewood oil. This bath oil contains African Marula oil, Camellia oil and sunflower oil which are naturally rich in antioxidants and essential fatty acids to help reveal a soft and youthful complexion.</description></item><item><title>La Premiere Body Wash Collection</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-premiere-body-wash-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:50:56 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-premiere-body-wash-collection/</guid><description>La Première: Gently cleanse with this fragrance-Free and pH balanced body wash, formulated with organic Rose petal water and a unique blend of organic ingredients. Soap free, sulfate free and non-drying to cleanse and comfort the most delicate of skin. Skin stays hydrated, smooth and revived. Suitable for all skin types, especially sensitive skin or even Eczema. Scents of Mediterranean: A blend of refreshingly relaxing essential oils brings the skin a true scent of Mediterranean.</description></item><item><title>La Premier Body Treatment Oil Collection</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-premiere-body-treatment-oil-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:20:04 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-premiere-body-treatment-oil-collection/</guid><description>Indulge the scent of freshness, Our Mediterranean Hyssop oil has anti bacterial benefit and remarkably helps acne-prone skin heal faster. It helps address undesirable ingrown hair and tighten pores, making skin smoother and softer. Combined with organic German blue chamomile, this fast-absorbing body treatment oil soothes and clams skin without greasiness. Skin stay soft and revived. Suitable for all skin types.
Mediterranean hyssop body treatment oil: size : 150 ml.</description></item><item><title>Le Soleil Body</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-soleil-body/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:17:31 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-soleil-body/</guid><description>The revolutioary Le Soleil Body protection uses a specially developed proprietary enwrapping technique to stabilize the organic sunscreens and to ensure high performance with prolonged and consistent SPF values. The aqueous encapsulated Sunscreen is non-irritant, waterproof and not absorbed into the skin, and can also provide a longer skin surface residence time as well as reproducible SPF values with broad spectrum protection (PA++++). Formulated with organic extract and brightening Kakadu plum extract which is the richest natural source of vitamin C, this sunscreen serum helps brighten and repair damaged skin while leaving skin comfortable all day long.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:05:08 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/contact-us/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:02:29 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/about-us/</guid><description>A quest for perfect balance between sustainable beauty, precious gifts from nature and urban lifestyle empowers us to create Brisuthi, commonly defined as &amp;ldquo;Pure in Thai&amp;rdquo;.
We are attracted by organic beauty and strong passion inspired by nature that gives us the most precious a finest ingredients. This integration crystalizes a true scent of organic beauty and leads us to create the line that is simple, minimal, luxurious, yet miraculously effective without adding colors, perfumes, parabens or unnecessary chemical substances.</description></item><item><title>Press</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/press/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 19:33:53 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/press/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>