<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Treat on Brisuthi</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/treat/</link><description>Recent content in Treat on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 17:02:41 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/treat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aboriginal Citrus Concentrate</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/aboriginal-citrus-concentrate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:03:45 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/aboriginal-citrus-concentrate/</guid><description>Superior potency with highest concentrations of natural Phyto-actives derived from organic plants with innovative cellular extraction. This concentrate serum contains Murunga extract (a native tree from Australia) which is the richest source of natural Vitamin C found in nature and provide Phyto-active compounds, including Gallic acid and Flavone Glycoside which helps stabilize Vitamin C. Combined with Finger lime caviar extract which boasts the great amount of Ferulic acid, Coumarin and Tryptophan, This powerful global anti-aging concentrate helps rejuvenate skin.</description></item><item><title>White Cypress Intensive Radiance Treatment Serum</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/white-cypress-intensive-radiance-treatment-serum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:01:20 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/white-cypress-intensive-radiance-treatment-serum/</guid><description>An fast-correcting serum clinically proven to combat hyper-pigmentation, fade dark spots and repair sun damage, formulated with a powerful blend of organic actives &amp;amp; nutrients, including White Cypress, Snowflower, Desert lime and Davidson plum, which provide full profile of Phyto actives; Procyanidin, Epicatechin, Kaempferol. To ensure the fast acting, this serum is fomulated with a traditional Chinese herb Rheum rhaponticum root extract which tightly controls melanin synthesis. Within 2 weeks of consistent use, skin looks visibly brighter, more luminous and toned.</description></item><item><title>Kalahari Global Anti-Aging Treatment Oil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/kalahari-global-anti-aging-treatment-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:55:13 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/kalahari-global-anti-aging-treatment-oil/</guid><description>The global anti-aging treatment, infused with organic Melon, Watermelon and Guava seed oil from Kalahari Desert of Namibia is a rich natural source of broad-spectrum antioxidants (A, B, C, D, E, F) amino Acids glutamate and tryptophan acid and vital minerals. It can visibly lift, tone and tighten skin with natural Arginine and Lysine. These peptides relax facial muscles just like having a Botox. Thanks to its rich Omega 6 fatty acids, the oil penetrates deeply to help rejuvenate and create healthy glowing skin by stimulating skin cell growth and restructuring skin cells to keep skin supple, firm, and youthfully radiant.</description></item><item><title>Huile De Nuit</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/huile-de-nuit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:53:30 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/huile-de-nuit/</guid><description>Huile de nuit is an exceptional global anti-aging treatment with organically wild-crafted Buriti oil (the richest natural source of pro-vitamin A), super-antioxidant Açaí fruit oil and exceptional antiaging cacay oil. Thanks to its vitamins and minerals concentrate, This Oil fight all signs of aging and helps visibly promote luminosity, replenish moisture, restore elasticity, and remarkably repair lines and wrinkles. After few nights of use, skin is gently retexturized and rejuvenated, leaving a brighter, luminous, healthy-looking complexion in the morning</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Prickly Pear Oil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-prickly-pear-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:44:51 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-prickly-pear-oil/</guid><description>The heritage of Morocco Prickly pear seed oil, one of the most expensive oils in the world contains almost 150% more vitamin E than Argan oil. This naturally occurring antioxidant acts as a free radical scavenger, preventing them from causing damage that leads to signs of aging. It benefits the skin with it’s exceptional hydrating, brightening and global anti-aging properties. The production of premium Prickly Pear Seed Oil is incredibly labour intensive and time consuming — it takes nearly 30 kilograms of seed, or 8 tons of the fruit, to produce just one litre of oil.</description></item></channel></rss>