<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cleanse on Brisuthi</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/cleanse/</link><description>Recent content in Cleanse on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 16:57:31 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/cleanse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moroccan Saffron Water</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-saffron-water/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:40:51 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-saffron-water/</guid><description>Organic Moroccan Saffron is a well-known for the most expensive spice and has a lot of health benefits and therapeutic values. The subtly aromatic spice is one of the most prominent ingredients used in skin lightening agent due to copper, magnesium, potassium, magnese, iron, selenium, zinc as well as vitamin C, riboflavin,niacin (vitamin B), folic acid and vitamin A contents. Formulated with organic Aloe vera Barbadensis Miller which contains both Aloin A and B, This Essence water can help skin reach its youthfully radiant.</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Rose Damascus Water</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-rose-damascus-water/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 19:43:32 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-rose-damascus-water/</guid><description>Made by hand in Morocco by one of the oldest women’s co-operatives, using only the finest roses which have been grown organically in a pesticide free zone. The water is triple distilled, filtered and infused with rose petals. This is a 100% natural and organic product. Free from parabens, preservatives, fragrances, binders, additives, colorants and any other nasties. Our 100% pure and Certified Organic by Ecocert Moroccan Rose Damascus water contains natural anti-inflammatory properties to reduce redness and skin irritation, soften, balance and regenerate your face, as well as tighten and minimize pores.</description></item><item><title>African Baobab Oil Treatment Cleanser</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/african-baobab-oil-treatment-cleanser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 19:43:12 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/african-baobab-oil-treatment-cleanser/</guid><description>Our cult product African Baobab Oil Cleanser gently dissolves all makeup, helps unclog pore and leaves skin remarkably clean, refreshed and balanced without a trace of makeup. Infused with “Tree of life “Organic Baobab oil which is very rich in nutrients – contains all three omega fatty acids: omega 3, 6 and 9, as well as containing some rare fatty acids and a host of vitamin A, C, D, E and combined with organic Hempseed oil and organic Sacha Inchi oil which has the highest amount of Liolenic acid in the world.</description></item><item><title>French Geranium Foaming Cleanser</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/french-geranium-foaming-cleanser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 19:41:31 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/french-geranium-foaming-cleanser/</guid><description>This Sulfate-free foaming cleanser gently dissolves impurities without striping moisture. Its pH equals to pure water (pH7) and provides you delicate lather. Formulated with soothing agent and natural extracts, along with Geranium essential oil, Rose damascus, Roman Chamomile, Cactus and Royal lotus pollen extract. This cleanser is suitable for all skin types, even acne-prone skin.</description></item></channel></rss>