<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Body on Brisuthi</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/categories/body/</link><description>Recent content in Body on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:12:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/categories/body/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Egyptian Myrrh Bath Oil</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/egyptian-myrrh-bath-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:53:56 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/egyptian-myrrh-bath-oil/</guid><description>Indulge yourself with a luxurious bathe exprerience to pamper, and moisturize the skin. Treat your body to a relaxing bath in our unique scent blended with Egyptian myrrh oil and uplifting Rosewood oil. This bath oil contains African Marula oil, Camellia oil and sunflower oil which are naturally rich in antioxidants and essential fatty acids to help reveal a soft and youthful complexion.</description></item><item><title>La Premiere Body Wash Collection</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/la-premiere-body-wash-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:50:56 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/la-premiere-body-wash-collection/</guid><description>La Première: Gently cleanse with this fragrance-Free and pH balanced body wash, formulated with organic Rose petal water and a unique blend of organic ingredients. Soap free, sulfate free and non-drying to cleanse and comfort the most delicate of skin. Skin stays hydrated, smooth and revived. Suitable for all skin types, especially sensitive skin or even Eczema. Scents of Mediterranean: A blend of refreshingly relaxing essential oils brings the skin a true scent of Mediterranean.</description></item><item><title>La Premier Body Treatment Oil Collection</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/la-premiere-body-treatment-oil-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:20:04 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/la-premiere-body-treatment-oil-collection/</guid><description>Mediterranean hyssop body treatment oil: size : 150 ml.
price : 1,490 baht
Indulge the scent of freshness, Our Mediterranean Hyssop oil has anti bacterial benefit and remarkably helps acne-prone skin heal faster. It helps address undesirable ingrown hair and tighten pores, making skin smoother and softer. Combined with organic German blue chamomile, this fast-absorbing body treatment oil soothes and clams skin without greasiness. Skin stay soft and revived.</description></item><item><title>Le Soliel Body</title><link>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/le-soliel-body/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:17:31 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://paiboon15721.github.io/brisuthi/product/le-soliel-body/</guid><description>The revolutioary Le Soleil Body protection uses a specially developed proprietary enwrapping technique to stabilize the organic sunscreens and to ensure high performance with prolonged and consistent SPF values. The aqueous encapsulated Sunscreen is non-irritant, waterproof and not absorbed into the skin, and can also provide a longer skin surface residence time as well as reproducible SPF values with broad spectrum protection (PA++++). Formulated with organic extract and brightening Kakadu plum extract which is the richest natural source of vitamin C, this sunscreen serum helps brighten and repair damaged skin while leaving skin comfortable all day long.</description></item></channel></rss>