<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mask on Brisuthi</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/mask/</link><description>Recent content in Mask on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 18:34:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/mask/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sandalwood Exfoliating Mask</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/sandalwood-exfoliating-mask/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:15:52 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/sandalwood-exfoliating-mask/</guid><description>A super fine sandalwood exfoliating mask loaded with organic extracts gently polishes, refines, and improves the appearance of skin’s texture while Pink Brazilian clay helps unclog pores and remove all impurities and toxins to reveal a brighter and younger looking complexion.</description></item><item><title>Le Mask Noir</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-mask-noir/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:14:33 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-mask-noir/</guid><description>The Rinse-off mask is formulated with Ghassoul clay which forms naturally in the Atlas regions of Morocco. This clay has been used for centuries as a tradition to gently cleanse impurities from the skin and hair. Rich in vitamins, minerals and trace elements such as iron, zinc, magnesium, phosphorous. Ghassoul has cleansing, soothing, absorbing and regenerative properties. Infused with Cactus extract, Glabridin derived naturally from Licorice root and various organic and natural extracts, This intensive clay mask contains high levels of antioxidants that calm inflammation and promotes skin radiance.</description></item><item><title>Intensive Radiance Treatment Mask</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/intensive-radiance-treatment-mask/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 18:34:05 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/intensive-radiance-treatment-mask/</guid><description>Developed with a naturally-derived sheet made from amino acid-rice fermented rice fermented rice, this exceptional facial treatment mask is formulated with maximum dose of finger lime caviar extract and Davidson plum which are packed with remarkable photo-active compounds including tartaric acid, gallic acid, quercetin and anthocyanin the synergism of these powerful compounds delivers intensive brightening and anti-aging benefits. Other natural ingredients including comfrey extract and snowblower extract heal and soothe irritated skin and stimulate hydration production after 20 minutes of use, skin becomes more youthfully radiant, firmer and smoother.</description></item></channel></rss>