<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Moisture on Brisuthi</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/moisture/</link><description>Recent content in Moisture on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 17:03:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/moisture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Le Soleil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-soleil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:13:39 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/le-soleil/</guid><description>The revolutioary Le Soleil The ultimate protection uses a specially developed proprietary enwrapping technique to stabilize the organic sunscreens and to ensure high performance with prolonged and consistent SPF values. The aqueous encapsulated Sunscreen is non-irritant and not absorbed into the skin, and can also provide a longer skin surface residence time as well as reproducible SPF values with broad spectrum protection (PA++++). Formulated with one of the most Super antioxidants, Hydroxytyrosol and Oleuropein naturally derived from olive fruit and leaf, the sunscreen helps preserve the skin’s ability to protect against the sun and photo-aging due to a combination of cutting-edge protective super antioxidant ingredients and natural Ectoin and SOD, one of the most powerful antipollution agent.</description></item><item><title>La Creme Intensive Global Anti Aging Treatment</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-creme-intensive-global-anti-aging-treatment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:12:12 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-creme-intensive-global-anti-aging-treatment/</guid><description>The exquisite modern gel-cream is designed to combat all signs of aging. An intelligent formula is infused with innovative NoHyal, a new generation of Hyaluronic acid which is more efficient than Retinol. Combined with organic Ximenynic acid-rich Sandalwood seed oil, this cream can reduce fine lines, improve skin tone, provide long-lasting hydration and increase dermal strength. While other organic extracts help retexturize and reveal more youthful and brighter skin. Moreover, French Melon extract provides the exceptional protection from aggressive environment with SOD, one of the most powerful antioxidants.</description></item><item><title>Balloon Vine Intensive Repair Treatment</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/brazillian-balloon-vine-intensive-repair-treatment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:08:25 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/brazillian-balloon-vine-intensive-repair-treatment/</guid><description>Harness the power of the nature with organic Balloon vine extract and 12 powerful plant extracts, This intensive repair treatment create a complex that reduces inflammation and Irritation, protects and stabilizes the aggrieved skin-barrier with natural Phytosterols which can effectively reduce inflammation, almost equal to 0.1% hydrocortisone while antioxidants soothe and effectively addresse skin problems, including redness, itchiness or chronic breakouts. It works strategically to strengthen the skin in order to achieve a healthy and flawless skin.</description></item><item><title>La Creme Yeux Concentrate Eye Contour Treatment</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-creme-yeux-concentrate-eye-contour-treatment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:58:35 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/la-creme-yeux-concentrate-eye-contour-treatment/</guid><description>An exceptional nourishing eye cream rich in advanced natural extracts, including Super green Broccoli extract and Mountain Pepper berry,that work to instantly make skin around the eyes look smoother and firmer. Infused with Hyalusphere® encapsulated in a patented Spherulite and Arabica green coffee bean extract which has an incredible high level of chlorogenic acid, a powerful antioxidant. This eye treatment can obviously help reduce the look of fine lines, dark circles, and puffiness.</description></item></channel></rss>