<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tone on Brisuthi</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/tone/</link><description>Recent content in Tone on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 18:51:46 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/tone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moroccan Saffron Water</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-saffron-water/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:40:51 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-saffron-water/</guid><description>Organic Moroccan Saffron is a well-known for the most expensive spice and has a lot of health benefits and therapeutic values. The subtly aromatic spice is one of the most prominent ingredients used in skin lightening agent due to copper, magnesium, potassium, magnese, iron, selenium, zinc as well as vitamin C, riboflavin,niacin (vitamin B), folic acid and vitamin A contents. Formulated with organic Aloe vera Barbadensis Miller which contains both Aloin A and B, This Essence water can help skin reach its youthfully radiant.</description></item><item><title>Moroccan Rose Damascus Water</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-rose-damascus-water/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 19:43:32 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/moroccan-rose-damascus-water/</guid><description>Made by hand in Morocco by one of the oldest women’s co-operatives, using only the finest roses which have been grown organically in a pesticide free zone. The water is triple distilled, filtered and infused with rose petals. This is a 100% natural and organic product. Free from parabens, preservatives, fragrances, binders, additives, colorants and any other nasties. Our 100% pure and Certified Organic by Ecocert Moroccan Rose Damascus water contains natural anti-inflammatory properties to reduce redness and skin irritation, soften, balance and regenerate your face, as well as tighten and minimize pores.</description></item></channel></rss>