<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Highlight on Brisuthi</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/highlight/</link><description>Recent content in Highlight on Brisuthi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:58:37 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brisuthi.com/tags/highlight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>African Baobab Oil Treatment Cleanser</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/african-baobab-oil-treatment-cleanser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 19:43:12 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/african-baobab-oil-treatment-cleanser/</guid><description>Our cult product African Baobab Oil treatment Cleanser gently dissolves all makeup, helps unclog pore and leaves skin remarkably clean, refreshed and balanced without a trace of makeup. Infused with “Tree of life “Organic Baobab oil which is very rich in nutrients – contains all three omega fatty acids: omega 3, 6 and 9, as well as containing some rare fatty acids and a host of vitamin A, C, D, E.</description></item><item><title>Huile De Nuit</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/huile-de-nuit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 12:53:30 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/huile-de-nuit/</guid><description>Huile de nuit is an exceptional global anti-aging treatment with organically wild-crafted Buriti oil (the richest natural source of pro-vitamin A), super-antioxidant Açaí fruit oil and exceptional antiaging cacay oil. Thanks to its vitamins and minerals concentrate, This Oil fight all signs of aging and helps visibly promote luminosity, replenish moisture, restore elasticity, and remarkably repair lines and wrinkles. After few nights of use, skin is gently retexturized and rejuvenated, leaving a brighter, luminous, healthy-looking complexion in the morning</description></item><item><title>L&#39;Huile De Ungurahua Hair Treatment Oil</title><link>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/l-huile-de-ungurahua-hair-treatment-oil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:58:37 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://www.brisuthi.com/product/l-huile-de-ungurahua-hair-treatment-oil/</guid><description>Organically-wildcrafted Ungurahua oil is an exceptional hair treatment which can addresses scalp problems, especially itchy dandruff and hair loss. It stimulates and regenerates follicle cells, thus controlling scalp disorders caused by bacterial infections and increasing circulation and capillary strength. Infused with Organically-wildcrafted Pequi Oil which has amazing capacity to restore the hair&amp;rsquo;s fiber after chemical and heat damage. It brings back silkiness, malleability, and shine to the hair while an exclusive blended essential oil helps stimulate hair growth and keeps scalp healthy.</description></item></channel></rss>